<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>

<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="ut.xsl"?>

<catalog>
<ut>
		<title>Asian Paints</title>
		<about>Asian Paints is India’s largest paint company and Asia’s third largest paint company, with a turnover of Rs 109.70 billion. The group has an enviable reputation in the corporate world for professionalism, fast track growth, and building shareholder equity. Asian Paints operates in 17 countries and has 25 paint manufacturing facilities in the world servicing consumers in over 65 countries. Besides Asian Paints, the group operates around the world through its subsidiaries Berger International Limited, Apco Coatings, SCIB Paints and Taubmans.Asian Paints was included in Forbes Asia’s ‘Fab 50’ list of Companies in Asia Pacific in 2011, 2012 and 2013. Forbes Global magazine USA ranked Asian Paints among the ‘200 Best Small Companies in the World’ for 2002 and 2003 and presented the 'Best under a Billion' award, to the company. Asian Paints is the only paint company in the world to receive this recognition. Forbes has also ranked Asian Paints among the ‘Best under a Billion companies in Asia’ in 2005, 2006 and 2007. The company has come a long way since its small beginnings in 1942. Four friends who were willing to take on the world's biggest, most famous paint companies operating in India at that time set it up as a partnership firm. Over the course of 25 years Asian Paints became a corporate force and India's leading paints company. Driven by its strong consumer-focus and innovative spirit, the company has been the market leader in paints since 1967. Today it is double the size of any other paint company in India. Asian Paints manufactures a wide range of paints for Decorative and Industrial use. In Decorative paints, Asian Paints is present in all the four segments v.i.z Interior Wall Finishes, Exterior Wall Finishes, Enamels and Wood Finishes. It also introduced many innovative concepts in the Indian paint industry like Colour Worlds (Dealer Tinting Systems), Home Solutions (painting solutions Service), Kids World (painting solutions for kid’s room), Colour Next (Prediction of Colour Trends through in-depth research) and Royale Play Special Effect Paints, just to name a few. Asian Paints has always been ahead when it comes to providing consumer experience. It has set up a Signature Store in Mumbai and Delhi in India, where consumers are educated on colours and how it can change their homes. Vertical integration has seen it diversify into products such as Phthalic Anhydride and Pentaerythritol, which are used in the paint manufacturing process. Asian Paints also operates through ‘PPG Asian Paints Pvt Ltd’ (50:50 JV between Asian Paints and PPG Inc, USA, one of the largest automotive coatings manufacturer in the world) to service the increasing requirements of the Indian automotive coatings market. Asian Paints has formed another 50:50 JV with PPG named ‘Asian Paints PPG Pvt Ltd’ to service the protective, industrial powder, industrial containers and light industrial coatings markets.

</about>
		</ut>
</catalog>