<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>

<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="ut.xsl"?>

<catalog>
<ut>
		<title>Havells India Limited</title>
		<about>


Havells India Limited is a $1.3 Billion leading Fast Moving Electrical Goods (FMEG) Company with a strong global footprint. Havells enjoys enviable market dominance across a wide spectrum of products, including Industrial and Domestic Circuit Protection Devices, Cables and Wires, Motors, Fans, Modular Switches, Home Appliances, Electric Water Heaters, Power Capacitors, CFL Lamps, Luminaires for Domestic, Commercial and industrial Applications.


Havells in 2007 created history by acquiring world’s renowned lighting company Sylvania thus registering itself amongst top 4 lighting companies in the world. Today, Havells owns some of the most prestigious global brands like Havells, Crabtree, Sylvania, Concord, Luminance and Standard. Its global network constitutes of 6500 professionals across 91 branches and representative offices in over 50 countries. Its 11 state-of-the-art manufacturing plants in India located at Haridwar, Baddi, Noida, Sahibabad, Faridabad, Alwar, Neemrana and 7 world class manufacturing plants located in Europe, Latin America, Africa and China are manufacturing globally acclaimed products, synonymous with excellence and precision in the electrical industry.


A 20000 strong global distribution network continuously strives to set new benchmarks in prompt delivery and service to customers – powering their smiles like none other electrical brand in the country. Further to this the company pioneered the concept of exclusive brand showroom in the electrical industry with ‘Havells Galaxy’. Today over 210 Havells Galaxies across the country are helping customers, both domestic and commercial, to choose from a wide variety of products for different applications. Havells became the first FMEG Company to offer door step service via its initiative ‘Havells Connect’.  Thanks to the quality of products and quicker service, it has minimum customer complaints and highest customer satisfaction.

</about>
		</ut>
</catalog>