<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>

<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="ut.xsl"?>

<catalog>
<ut>
		<title>Infosys</title>
		<about>


Building Tomorrow’s Enterprise

Infosys is a global leader in consulting, technology and outsourcing solutions. As a proven partner focused on building tomorrow's enterprise, Infosys enables clients in more than 30 countries to outperform the competition and stay ahead of the innovation curve. With US$7.906bn in LTM Q2 FY14 revenues and 160,000+ employees, Infosys provides enterprises with strategic insights on what lies ahead. We help enterprises transform and thrive in a changing world through strategic consulting, operational leadership and the co-creation of breakthrough solutions, including those in mobility, sustainability, big data and cloud computing.

The Infosys Story

In 1981, seven engineers started Infosys Limited with just US$250. From the beginning, the company was founded on the principle of building and implementing great ideas that drive progress for clients and enhance lives through enterprise solutions. For over three decades, we have been a company focused on bringing to life great ideas and enterprise solutions that drive progress for our clients.

We recognize the importance of nurturing relationships that reflect our culture of unwavering ethics and mutual respect. It’ll come as no surprise, then, that 98 percent (as of September 30, 2013) of our revenues come from existing clients.

Infosys has a growing global presence with more than 160,000+ employees worldwide, across 73 offices and 94 development centers in the United States, India, China, Australia, Japan, Middle East, and Europe.

At Infosys, we believe our responsibilities also extend beyond business. That’s why we established the Infosys Foundation to provide assistance to some of the most socially and economically depressed sectors of the communities in which we work. And it's why we behave ethically and honestly in all our interactions – with our clients, our partners and our employees.

</about>
		</ut>
</catalog>