<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>

<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="ut.xsl"?>

<catalog>
<ut>
		<title>Jaypee Associates</title>
		<about>



The Jaypee Group is a  20,000 crore well diversified infrastructural industrial conglomerate based in Noida, India. It was founded by Jaiprakash Gaur which is involved in well diversified infrastructure conglomerate with business interests in Engineering and Construction, Power, Cement, Real Estate, Hospitality, Expressways, Sports and Education (not-for-profit).
Jaypee is India's third largest cement producer and the largest private sector hydropower company with 1,700 MW in operation. The Jaypee Group successfully completed projects in 18 states of India and Bhutan. Jaypee is the engineering and construction company for India's Yamuna Expressway, which opened 9 August 2012.
JIL, the group flagship, has an engineering and construction wing which mostly supports Jaypee projects. It also has the largest land bank in India's National Capital Region, i.e., New Delhi. Jaypee has four thermal power plants totalling 5,120 MW under construction, and these are slated to go on stream by December 2014.

Jaiprakash Gaur, founder and chairman of Jaiprakash Associates Limited after acquiring a Diploma in Civil Engineering in 1950 from the University of Roorkee—now called the Indian Institute of Technology Roorkee (IITR)—in Roorkee, Uttarakhand, had a stint with the Uttar Pradesh government and branched off on his own, to start as a civil contractor in 1958, group is the third largest cement producer in the country. The groups cement facilities are located today all over India in 10 states, with 18 plants having an aggregate cement production capacity of 24 million tonnes and same is poised to become 36 million Tonnes before October 2011.
A penalty of Rs1 billion was imposed on the group by the Green Bench of Himachal Pradesh High Court for setting up a cement plant and a captive thermal power station in the state.


</about>
		</ut>
</catalog>