<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>

<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="ut.xsl"?>

<catalog>
<ut>
		<title>Jindal Steel and Power Limited (JSPL)</title>
		<about>


Jindal Steel and Power Limited (JSPL) is one of India's major steel producers with a significant presence in sectors like Mining, Power Generation and Infrastructure.

With an annual turnover of over US$ 3.6 billion, JSPL is a part of the 
US$ 18 billion diversified O. P. Jindal Group and is consistently tapping new opportunities by increasing production capacity, diversifying investments, and leveraging its core capabilities to venture into new businesses. The company has committed investments exceeding US$ 30 billion in the future and has several business initiatives running simultaneously across continents.

Mr. Naveen Jindal, the youngest son of the legendary Shri. O. P. Jindal spearheads JSPL and its group companies. The company produces economical and efficient steel and power through backward and forward integration.

From the widest flat products to a whole range of long products, JSPL today sports a product portfolio that caters to varied needs in the steel market. The company also has the distinction of producing the world's longest 121 metre rails and large size parallel flange beams for the first time in India.

Corporate Profile
JSPL operates the largest coal - based sponge iron plant in the world and has an installed capacity of 3 MTPA of steel at Raigarh in Chhattisgarh. With a 0.6 MTPA Wire Rod Mill and a 1.0 MTPA capacity Bar Mill at Patratu, Jharkhand, a medium and light structural mill at Raigarh, Chhattisgarh and a 1.5 MTPA Steel Melting Shop and a Plate Mill to produce upto 5.00 metre wide plates at Angul, Odisha. The company aims for a fast-paced growth so as to contribute substantially to India's long term prosperity.

An enterprising spirit and the ability to discern future trends have been the driving force behind the company's remarkable growth story. The company has scaled new heights with the combined force of innovation, adaptation of new technologies and the collective skills of its 15,000 strong, committed workforce.

</about>
		</ut>
</catalog>