<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>

<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="ut.xsl"?>

<catalog>
<ut>
		<title>Maruti Suzuki</title>
		<about>


If you’ve gone from here to there or just about anywhere in India, chances are you’ve driven with us. For over 3 decades now, we’ve been going places with India.

1982. Gurgaon, Haryana. Little did this quiet suburb of New Delhi know that it was to become the seat of India’s automobile revolution, at the Maruti Suzuki factory.

In 1982, India turned out just 40,000 cars every year. The Maruti 800 rolled out and a new chapter began.

Ours was a story of an obsession with customer delight, unheard of until then.

It was about a commitment to create value. Of innovation, quality, creativity, partnerships, openness and learning.

It was a new story of leadership. Today, Maruti Suzuki alone makes 1.5 million cars every year. That’s one car every 12 seconds. Head and shoulders above the rest, which includes every major global auto company.

It was also the story of a motoring revolution-cars that delivered great performance, efficiency and environment friendliness with low cost of ownership. A story built on Suzuki’s belief in small cars for a big future. One that enabled millions of Indians to make driving a way of life. Indians, and India, got into the driver’s seat, and we were happy to drive with them in the fast lane.

So what drives us? Our relationship with the millions of Indians who drive us. Our team of over 9000 dedicated and passionate professionals. That turn out 17 cars with over 150 variants. Backed by a nationwide service network spanning 1422 Cities and towns and Sales network spread across 878 cities. 2 state-of-the-art factories, at Manesar and Gurgaon. A diesel engine plant with capacity upped. To turn out 7 lakh diesel cars a year. And a commitment to road safety that is making India’s roads safer.

But millions of miles later, our driving inspiration comes from one place. India’s hopes, dreams and aspirations.

It’s been a great journey so far. And it feels like we’ve only just begun.

</about>
		</ut>
</catalog>